AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - MN-1319b: Basic Swimming Techniques--Elementary Tactics of Life Saving, undated; AV2950; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Container label reads: "United States Navy, Bureau of Aeronautics. Training Film Section, Photographic Division." (Box 78, Reel 2,950)
    New York University |x Athletics.; United States. Navy
  - NYU vs. Dartmouth College (basketball), 2 January 1950; AV2951; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Winik Films Corporation. (Box 78, Reel 2,951)
    Madison Square Garden. (New York, N.Y.: 1925-1968).; Basketball.; New York University |x Athletics.
  - NYU Basketball, unknown; AV2952; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,952)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame (basketball), 1950 February 27; AV2953; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,953)
  - NYU Basketball [unidentified], undated; AV2954; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,954)
    Condition Note
    This film has severe Vinegar Syndrome. It is too warped to inspect or remove from the reel. CANNOT BE LOOKED AT.
  - Sunrise Semester: Middle East (Reel 1 of 2), 1950; AV2955; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,955)
  - Sunrise Semester: Middle East (Reel 2 of 2), 1950; AV2956; Original Format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2956)
  - NYU vs. Southern Methodist University (Reel 3), 1946-1947; AV2957; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,957)
  - Fordham vs. NYU, 1951; AV2958; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,958)
  - Berlin Olympics (track, gymnastics), 1936; AV2959; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,959)
    Gymnastics.; New York University |x Athletics.; Olympics.
  - NYU vs. University of Oklahoma (basketball), 1951 December 22; AV2960; Original Format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,960)
  - NYU vs. Southern Methodist University (Reel 2), 1946-1947; AV2961; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,961)
  - NYU vs. Colgate University (basketball), 1950 December 12; AV2962; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,962)
  - University of Cincinnati vs St. Bonaventure University (basketball), 1957-1958; AV2963; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,963)
  - NYU vs. City College of New York, undated; AV2965; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,965)
  - NYU vs. Syracuse University (basketball), 1940-1941; AV2967; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,967)
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. PMC, 1940; AV2968; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Container label reads: #28 (Box 80, Reel 2,968)
  - NYU vs. Brigham Young University (Reel 1), 19 March 1966; AV2972; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Winik Films Corporation. (Box 80, Reel 2,972)
    This item is related to RG 41.1, Records of the Basketball Program, Department of Athletics.
  - NYU football practice, undated; AV2964; Original format: 16mm film (Box 79, Reel 2,964)
  - NI-1, unknown; AV2970; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,970)
  - [Unidentified Loop], unknown; AV2975; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,975)
  - NYU vs. University of Oregon (Reel 3), 1946-47; AV2976; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,976)
  - NYU vs. University of Oregon (Reel 2), 1946; AV2977; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,977)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame (Reel 3), 1947; AV2978; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,978)
  - NYU vs. Syracuse University, 17 December 1959; AV2979; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,979)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame, 1949-50; AV2980; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,980)
    This item is related to RG41, records of the Deparment of Athletics
  - NYU vs. Duke University, 1946-47; AV2981; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,981)
  - NYU vs. Colgate University, 12 December 1950; AV2982; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Winik Films Corporation. (Box 80, Reel 2,982)
  - NYU vs. Duke University (Reel 1), 1946-47; AV2983; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film; Container label reads: 30-31 (Box 80, Reel 2,983)
    This item is related to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics.
  - NYU vs. Duke University (Reel 2), undated; AV2984; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,984)
    This item relates to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics.
  - unknown sports film, undated; AV2985; 1.0 film reels; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,985)
  - NYU 1-2 (L. Winik), unknown; AV2986; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,986)
  - NYU football [N1-12], undated; AV2989; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,989)
  - [#21 Football], unknown; AV2990; Original format: 16mm film (Box 80, Reel 2,990)
  - NYU football, unknown; AV2993 (Box 81, Reel 2,993)
    #8
  - NYU student demonstrations, October 17 1968; AV2994; Original format: Super 8mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,994)
  - Washington Square Campus, unknown; AV2995; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,995)
  - NYU - Washington Square, 1968 October 14; AV2996 (Box 81, Reel 2996)
  - NYU Bronx, unknown; AV2997; Original format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio (Box 81, Reel 2,997)
  - NYU football, undated; AV2998; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,998)
  - NYU vs. University of Notre Dame (Reel 3), 1948; AV2999; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 2,999)
  - NYU vs. University of Oklahoma (reel 1), 1951 December 22; AV3001; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,001)
  - NYU vs. Lafayette College (football), undated; AV3002; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,002)
  - NYU football, undated; AV3003; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,003)
    This item relates to RG41, records of the Department of Athletics
  - NYU vs. Temple University, undated; AV3004; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,004)
  - NYU wrestling, undated; AV3005; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,005)
  - NYU wrestling, undated; AV3006; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,006)
  - NYU Heights Campus, Nov 17 1968; AV3007; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,007)
  - NYU Washington Square Campus, Nov 17 1968; AV3008; Original format: 16mm film (Box 81, Reel 3,008)
  - NYU vs Notre Dame, 1953; AV3009; Original format: 16mm film (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,009)
  - NYU vs Manhattan, 1953; AV3010; Original format: 16 mm film (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,010)
  - NYU vs Springfield, 1948; AV3011 (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,011)
  - NYU vs Michigan, 1963; AV3012; Original format: 16mm film (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,012)
  - Penn vs Columbia, 1955-56; AV3013; Original format: 16mm film; phys desc? (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,013)
  - Columbia vs Princeton, 1957; AV3014; Original format: 16mm film (Box 82, Reel Reel 3,014)
  - Development: David B. Kriser Center, undated; AV3969 (Box 110, Item 3969)
  - Michael Harrington and Today's Other America (tape 1 of 2), undated; AV4268 (Box 116, Item 4268)
  - Michael Harrington and Today's Other America (tape 2 of 2), undated; AV4269 (Box 116, Item 4269)
  - Flying Saucer Mystery, 1950; AV5044 (Box 121, Item 5044)
  - Three Steps to Start, circa 1950s-1970s; AV5141; New York University. (Box 123, Reel 5141)
    This film is about adult education.
    These films were part of the Pennsylvania Department of Public Welfare’s lending library of public welfare-related films and were donated to NYU in September 2012.
    Original format: 16 mm film Print 1
  - A Child Went Forth, circa 1950s-1970s; AV5142; Leaf, Munro, 1905-1976; New York University. (Box 123, Reel 5142)
    Original format: 16mm Print 2
  - Prof. Raiken's class/Gallatin promo/Gallatin tape 13, undated; AV5144 (Box To be processed, Reel 5144)
  - unknown film from the Department of Athletics, undated; AV5145 (Reel 5145)
    This material is related to RG 41, Records of the Department of Athletics.
    Basketball.; Football.; New York University |x Athletics.
  - NYU vs. University of North Carolina (basketball), 1946-1947; AV5146 (Reel 5146)
  - NYU vs. University of Michigan, 1963; AV5147 (Reel 5147)
    Original format: 16 mm film
  - NYU (football), circa 1940; AV5148; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5148)
    Characteristics
    B&W; Silent
    Gauge
    Original Format: 16 mm film
  - NYU vs. Texas 1948 Reel 2, AV5149; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5149)
  - NYU vs. St. Josephs MSG 1/6/61, 1961; AV5150; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 8 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5150)
  - NYU vs. UMass 1st Round NCAA Philadelphia. 3/12/62, 1962; AV5151; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 8 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5151)
  - NYU vs. LaSalle 1962, AV5152; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 8 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5152)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (Videos #6-8), 1946-1962; AV5153; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5153)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (11-16), undated; AV5154; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5154)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (17-21), undated; AV5155; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5155)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (1-5), undated; AV5156; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5156)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (32-36), undated; AV5157; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5157)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (22-26), undated; AV5158; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5158)
  - NYU Athletics Compilation (27-31), undated; AV5159; B&W; Silent; Original Format: 16 mm film; 1 item (Box unknown, Reel 5159)